courts.com.sg 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy

JOIN HOME CLUB TITANIUM MEMBERSHIP

Join our HomeClub Titanium Membership at a launch promotion price of S$49 per year (U.P. S$69 per year)!

FIELDS MARKED WITH * ARE REQUIRED FIELDS

Title*

Name*

User Name*

ID Type*

Date Of Birth*

Nationality*

Gender*

Ethnic Group*

Marital Status*

Mobile No.*

Home No.*

Office No.*

Email*

Password*

Confirm Password*

Home Club No.*

Postal Code*

Block*

#

#

Street Name*

Condo/Apt Name*

OPTIONAL FIELDS

I agree to apply for HomeClub membership on the terms and conditions. I understand that I will be able to choose not to receive any promotional and marketing materials from Courts by changing my preferences via my online HomeClub account. I confirm that all information given by me in connection with this application is true and correct. 

COURTS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

Please make sure you read and understand this Policy. We may amend this Policy at any time. 

COURTS (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. (“Courts” or “we”) respects and protects the privacy of the users,visitors and people who purchase products on COURTS Online (whether from COURTS or from a third party Seller) (“you”). COURTS knows that you care how personal information about you is used and shared. By placing your Request, you agree that we may store, process, disclose and use data collected from you for the purposes of processing your Request and delivering your Goods. 

This Privacy Policy sets out what personal information we collect and how we use it. Referencesin this Policy to COURTS Online includes any website owned and operated by or on behalf of COURTS, including the COURTS Online Marketplace. 

BY VISITING COURTS ONLINE, OR BY REGISTERING AS A USER ON COURTS ONLINE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

### 1   HOW TO CONTACT US

Company Registration No. 197301411C   
GST Registration No. M20016265-0   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you may contact Customerservice@courts.com.sg. Or please write to us at Online Customer Service 50 Tampines North Drive 2, (S) 528766, or call us at 1800 222 6868 for any assistance you require. 

### 2   A WORD ABOUT CHILDREN

COURTS (and the third party Sellers) do not sell products for purchase by children. We (and third party Sellers) sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use COURTS Online only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

### 3   WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES COURTS COLLECT?

We may collect the following categories of personal information about you:

**3.1  Personal information that you provide to us on COURTS Online.** This includes anyinformation you provide on COURTS Online (for example when you register as a user or purchase a product on COURTS Online (whether from COURTS or from a third party Seller). This personal information will include your name, your address, your contact information and your payment information (and other kinds of personal information). Sometimes when you provide personal information on COURTS Online, you can choose not to provide certain personal information but this might limit our ability to provide certain features to you. You will be informed what information is required and what information is optional. 

**3.2   Personal information automatically provided to us.**We receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit COURTS Online. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses COURTS Online or advertisements and other content served on COURTS Online, if applicable. 

**3.3   Personal information provided from your devices.**If you download or use COURTS Online on a mobile device (this could be for example by using the COURTS Online app) and if have requested or consented to location services, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. Please refer to the user manual (or other information provided by manufacturer or software provider) for more information about how to do this.

**3.4   Personal information you provide to us via e-mail.**We often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from COURTS if your e-mail provider supports such capabilities. You may also provide us with personal information in the content of e-mails you send to us, as part of your day-to-day interactions with COURTS.You may choose to stop receiving or change the frequency of email, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications. You can update and correct your personal information anytime using My Account. Whenever we send you any information via enewletters, we will include instructions on how to unsubscribe and a one click link to do so. 

**3.5   Personal information from other sources.**From time to time we may receive information about you from other sources, for example from other users of COURTS Online including from third party Sellers. 

### 4   WHAT DOES COURTS DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

**4.1     **to handle orders (or to enable third party Sellers or providers of services to COURTS to do so); 

**4.2    **How to contact usto deliver products and services (or to enable third party Sellers or providers of services to COURTS to do so);

**4.3    **to communicate with you about orders, products, services (or to enable third party Sellers to do so);

**4.4    **to respond to your requests (or to enable third party Sellers to do so);

**4.5    ** to process payments;

**4.6    ** to communicate with you about promotional offers and to market to you;

**4.7    ** to update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us;

**4.8    ** to display content such as wish lists and customer reviews and recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you;

**4.9    ** to personalise and improve our services, and general offering to you, including COURTS Online; and

**4.10    **to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of COURTS Online and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

### 5   WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?

We send a "cookie" to your web browser. A "cookie" is a small data text file stored in the hard drive of your computer (if it so permits), which can be retrieved to identify you to COURTS. We do this to: enable our systems to recognise your device and to provide features to you; remember the information that you have previously entered, enabling us to customise COURTS Online to your preferences; and improve navigation and to collect aggregate information. These cookies will not give us any other personal information about you.   
Your Internet Service Provider allocates an IP address to your computer or device in order for it to access the Internet. The IP address is considered to be non-personal information and it may be dynamic (changing every time you connect to the Internet) or it may be static (unique to your computer). We collect your IP address. We do this to: diagnose server problems; and report aggregate information and determine the fastest route from your computer to COURTS Online.

### 6   DOES COURTS SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER PEOPLE?

COURTS does not sell or lease your personal information to third parties.  
We only use your information for the purposes set out in Section 4 of this Privacy Policy.  
We may share your information with the following third parties, where necessary and always in compliance with this Privacy Policy and with applicable laws.  
**6.1     Third party Sellers.** In order for the third party Sellers to provide their services to you when you purchase products or enquire about purchasing products from the third party Sellers.

**6.2     Third party service providers.** COURTS may need to share your information with certain third parties to perform services on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and providing customer service.

**6.3     Current or future COURTS entities or subsidiaries.**This includes without limitation our business partners and financial institutions, from time to time. These other parts of the courts business may be involved in providing certain services to you or supporting the provision of these services.

**6.4     Law enforcement agencies.**We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our rights; or protect the rights, property or safety of COURTS, our users or others including you.

### 7\.   THIRD PARTY SELLERS 

UNLESS OTHERWISE AUTHORISED OR CONSENTED TO BY COURTS, THIRD PARTY SELLERS MUST NOT NOT USE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IS ACCESSIBLE FROM COURTS ONLINE, EXCEPT TO ENTER INTO AND COMPLETE TRANSACTIONS CONDUCTED VIA COURTS ONLINE. THIRD PARTY SELLERS MUST NOT USE ANY SUCH INFORMATION FOR PURPOSES OF SOLICITATION, ADVERTISING, UNSOLICITED E-MAIL OR SPAMMING, HARASSMENT, INVASION OF PRIVACY OR OTHERWISE OBJECTIONABLE CONDUCT.

### 8\.   HOW SECURE IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

We shall take reasonable measures to ensure the confidentiality and security of the personal information shared with these third parties and to protect it from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  
It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

### 9\.   WHAT ABOUT THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS AND LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES? 

COURTS Online may include third party advertising and links to other websites. COURTS is not responsible for third party websites and you should find out from the other websites about their privacy policies.

### 10\.   WHAT INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS? 

You can access a broad range of your personal information by logging into your user account.

### 11\.   UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

You must make sure that the details you provide us with are correct and complete. You must inform us of any changes to the information you have provided. You can do this by logging into your user account.

### 12\.   MARKETING

You may choose to stop receiving or change the frequency of email, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your user account preferences or use the unsubscribe function on marketing materials.
